spikes.asia 2018-08-12

# Privacy Policy | Spikes Asia 2018

## **Privacy** & Cookie Policy

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

**1.1** This policy (the “Privacy Policy”) sets out the privacy and cookies policy of Asian Advertising Festival (Spikes Asia) Pte Ltd (“Ascential”. “we”, “us” or “our”).  Ascential is a company registered in Singapore with registration number 20090677 and registered office at 21 Media Circle #05-05, Infinite Studios, Singapore 138562.

**1.2**  For the purpose of applicable data protection and privacy laws (the “Privacy Laws”), and unless otherwise stated below, Ascential is the data controller in relation to the personal information covered by this Privacy Policy.

**1.3** Ascential is committed to protecting the privacy of its users.  The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe to you how Ascential will use personal information about you that is submitted to Ascential.  If at any time you wish to access, change or delete the personal information we hold about you or opt-out of or change the uses of your personal information, or if you wish us to transfer your data to a third party, please contact us at [unsubscribe@canneslions.com](mailto:unsubscribe@canneslions.com).

**1.4** Ascential may revise this Privacy Policy at any time by posting an update on its website(s). Please ensure that you check this website and any other Ascential website(s) you use from time to time to review the then current Privacy Policy and to update your preferences. This Privacy Policy was last updated in November 2017.

**2\. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**2.1** Depending on the circumstances in which we collect your information (as set out in paragraph 2.2 below) the types of personal information we collect and store may include your name, job title, place of work or study, date of birth, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, and/or credit/debit card details.

**2.2** Ascential (or third parties acting on Ascential’s behalf) may collect personal information about you in the following ways:

(a) when you complete and submit an application to Ascential to register on its website(s) or receive email alerts or other communications from Ascential;

(b) via postings to forums and blogs and any other posting that you make to a Ascential website (in such circumstances the information posted by you may, of course, also be available to users of the forum/blog/website throughout the world);

(c) during any transaction with us; and

(d) when you enquire about our activities, email, telephone or write to us or otherwise provide us with personal information.

**3\. STORAGE AND RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION**

**3.1** Ascential will keep your information securely. The technology that Ascential uses and the security policies which Ascential has implemented are intended to safeguard your information from unauthorised access and improper use. 

**3.2** Ascential will keep your information (to the extent permitted by the Privacy Laws) to enable Ascential to use it for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  We will keep your personal information for no longer than is needed for those purposes.

**4\. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

**4.1** Ascential may use your personal information to provide services to you, for example when you buy a festival pass.  Ascential may also use your personal information to further its legitimate interests, i.e. to help Ascential improves its services or for our direct marketing purposes.  

In more detail, we may include using your personal information for the following purposes:

(a) administering your website account(s) and otherwise in connection with any service for which you have provided your information, including any delegate pass, accommodation reservation, email alerts, transactions with us and competitions and promotions that you take part in;

(b) responding to any enquiry you make;

(c) sending you newsletters and/or alerts and information regarding Ascential’s services;

(d) Sending you important festival information, including but not limited to, speaker announcements, programme updates and invitations to special festival events;

(e) for generating aggregated statistics about users, traffic patterns etc. of the website and other services and developing Ascential's marketing plans.

**4.2** Ascential may also disclose your information (subject in each case to the requirements of the Privacy Laws) as follows:

(a) if you have given your consent for Ascential to do so, to other selected organisations to enable them to contact you or send you information by post, telephone and/or email;

(b) to third parties who are engaged by Ascential to exercise its rights under Clause 4.1;

(c) to third parties selected by Ascential as part of aggregated and anonymised statistics about users, traffic patterns etc. of the Ascential website(s);

(d) to such individuals and/or bodies as necessary to; ensure Ascential’s compliance with any applicable law, regulation, legal proceeding or governmental request;

(e) to third party providers as necessary to properly deal with your request, for example to accommodation providers where you have requested accommodation at a festival;

(f) (where you post material that does or may constitute a criminal offence, breach the rights of a third party, give rise to a civil action or breach the terms & conditions of the applicable website and as otherwise necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Ascential and its customers), to any relevant authority or third party requiring Ascential to disclose the identity of or locate anyone posting such material on an Ascential website; or

(g) to third parties selected by Ascential who will be present at Ascential events (e.g. selected festival sponsors) so that they can better plan the activities they offer to visitors to those events.

**4.3** If Ascential (or a relevant part of Ascential) is acquired by or merges with another company, your personal information may be passed to the purchasing/merging company amongst the transferred business assets. This will enable your relationship to continue with the relevant Ascential business despite the change of ownership. Your personal information may also be passed (on a confidential basis) to companies with whom Ascential is negotiating such a sale/merger as part of the verification exercise carried out on Ascential by the third party.

**4.4** In processing your information in accordance with the above, Ascential may (to the extent permitted by the Privacy Laws) send it outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). Ascential will take all reasonable steps to ensure that in such circumstances your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy but your attention is drawn to the fact that the laws of countries outside the EEA may provide lesser protection to your information than the UK.

**5\. COOKIES**

When you visit a Ascential website(s), Ascential uses “cookie” technology try to make that experience simple, personalised and meaningful. Cookies are small data files which are issued to your computer or any similar device you use to access the internet (e.g. smart phone, tablet or other mobile device) when you visit a website. Cookies store and sometimes track information about your use of the website. A number of cookies Ascential use last only for the duration of your web session and expire when you close your browser. Other cookies are used to remember you when you return to the website and will last for longer.

Ascential use cookies to:

(a) create a specific log-in session for a visitor to a Ascential website in order that page requests by that visitor are delivered in an effective, secure and consistent manner;

(b) recognise when a visitor to a Ascential website has visited before; this means we can identify the number of unique visitors we receive to the website and allows us to make sure we have enough capacity for the number of users that we get;

(c) customise elements of the promotional layout and/or content of the pages of the website;

(d) store your product selections to the shopping basket; and

(e) collect statistical information about how our visitors use the website(s) so that we can improve the website(s) and learn which parts are most popular to visitors;

(f) gather information through our advertising partners, about the pages on the Ascential website(s) that you visit, and also other information about other websites that you visit, so as to place you in an “interest segment”. This information is then used to serve interest-based advertisements which it is believed will be targeted to your interests. For more information about this type of interest based advertising, and about how to turn this feature off please visit <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/> or follow the link to the website of our advertising partners shown below. Without these cookies, advertisements you encounter will be less relevant to you and to your interests.

Some of the cookies used by Ascential websites are set by us, and some are set by third parties who are delivering services on our behalf. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that or to notify you each time a cookie is set. You can also learn more about cookies by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org which includes additional useful information on cookies and how to block cookies using different types of browser. Please note however, that by blocking or deleting cookies used on a Ascential website(s) you may not be able to take full advantage of the website(s) if you do so.

We have described the main cookies used on our website(s) below:

COOKIES THAT SUPPORT OUR WEB PLATFORM

"__RequestVerificationToken"  
This is an anti-forgery cookie set by web applications built using ASP.NET MVC technologies. It is designed to stop unauthorised posting of content to a website, known as Cross-Site Request Forgery. It holds no information about the user and is destroyed on closing the browser.

".ASPXAUTH"  
This cookie is used by sites using the .NET technology platform from Microsoft. It is commonly used to identify a logged-in user to enable access to secure areas of a site.

"ASP.NET_SessionId"  
General purpose platform session cookie, used by sites written with Microsoft .NET based technologies. Usually used to maintain an anonymised user session by the server.

"SC_ANALYTICS_GLOBAL_COOKIE"  
This cookie name is associated with the Sitecore Content Management System as is used for web analytics to identify repeat visits by unique users.

"dtCookie", "dtLatC", "dtPC"  
This cookie name is associated with software from Dynatrace, an application performance management (APM) software company. Their software manages the availability and performance of software applications and the impact on user experience in the form of deep transaction tracing, synthetic monitoring, real user monitoring, and network monitoring.

ANALYTICS COOKIES

"_ga"  
This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics - which is an update to Google's more commonly used analytics service. This cookie is used to distinguish unique users by assigning a randomly generated number as a client identifier. It is included in each page request in a site and used to calculate visitor, session and campaign data for the site’s analytics reports.

"_gid"  
This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics and stores a unique value for each page visited.

“PREF”, “VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE”, “YSC”  
YouTube uses these cookies to analyse traffic from embedded videos on our website(s).

MARKETING COOKIES

"_mkto_trk"  
This cookie is associated with an email marketing service provided by Marketo. This tracking cookie allows a website to link visitor behaviour to the recipient of an email marketing campaign, to measure campaign effectiveness.  
"com.silverpop.iMA.page_visit", "com.silverpop.iMA.session", "com.silverpop.iMAWebCookie"  
Used to support IBM Silverpop Engage email marketing, to permit newsletter activity and tracking.

"_CAN_BId"  
This cookie is set on sites using the CANDDi software from UK company Campaign and Digital Intelligence Ltd. The software provides the capacity to identify individuals visiting a site in real time, linked up directly with personal data held about the visitor, to improve sales conversion rates. This cookie contains a unique identifier for each visitor, enabling consistent tracking between visits.

"CAN_SId"  
This cookie is set on sites using the CANDDi software from UK company Campaign and Digital Intelligence Ltd. The software provides the capacity to identify individuals visiting a site in real time, linked up directly with personal data held about the visitor, to improve sales conversion rates. This cookie is a session identifier which enables tracking of visitors in a single browser session.

"ceg.s"  
This cookie name is associated with software provided by Crazy Egg Inc., a USA based company providing web analytics that tracks how visitors interact with pages on a site.

"ceg.u"  
This cookie name is associated with software provided by Crazy Egg Inc., a USA based company providing web analytics that tracks how visitors interact with pages on a site.

"OptimizelyBuckets"  
Cookie set by the Optimizely website optimisation platform. Used to store the page variants assigned to a user for A/B performance testing, to ensure the user gets a consistent experience.

"OptimizelyEndUserId"  
Cookie set by the Optimizely website optimisation platform. This cookie is a unique user identifier.

"OptimizelySegments"  
This cookie is set by the Optimizely website optimisation platform. It holds audience segmentation information for a visitor.

"_hjIncludedInSample"  
This cookie is associated with web analytics functionality and services from Hot Jar, a Malta based company. It uniquely identifies a visitor during a single browser session and indicates they are included in an audience sample.

"zarget_user_id"  
Zarget enables personalisation and testing for subsets of users. This cookie is set to collect information on user identification. This cookie is set only once upon visitor’s first page visit. Cookie expiration time is 30 days.

**6\. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Please be aware that Ascential does not control and is not responsible for websites that are referred to or linked from its own websites and that use of your personal information on these websites is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**7\. REGISTRATION**

**7.1** To access certain parts of the Ascential websites, Ascential may require you to register and provide certain information about yourself. 

**7.2** You are reminded that in addition to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, where you register you also agree to: 

(a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the relevant registration form (such information being the "Registration Data"); and

(b) maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it fully up to date.

**8\. TELEPHONE CALLS**

Please note your calls to Ascential may be recorded for training and quality control purposes.

**9\. QUESTIONS OR COMPLAINTS**

If you have questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personal information, please contact [unsubscribe@canneslions.com](mailto:unsubscribe@canneslions.com).  Under the Privacy Laws, you may also have a right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.  For more information, see the Information Commissioner’s website at [www.ico.org.uk](https://ico.org.uk/).
